<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[PREMIUM DIGITAL MARKETING STRATEGIES]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[PREMIUM DIGITAL MARKETING STRATEGIES]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/victormichael/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:26:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/victormichael/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1></h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6646052b3faa2e1c11960884fff4b42db34d2a4d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/victormichael/b704af44-7410-475c-a613-921ef971dadf/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b704af44-7410-475c-a613-921ef971dadf</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:09:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping Out Your Social Networking Goals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mapping Out Your Social Networking Goals</h1><p>Mapping Out Your Social Networking Goals
When setting out to achieve anything as a marketer, it is always important to have some set goals. These will not only point you in the right direction but will also outline your trajectory allowing you to look at the small steps you need to take to get where you need to be. Whatís more, they also allow you to measure your progress and to see whatís working and what isnít.
So how do you go about setting goals as a social media marketer? Letís break it downÖ
Numbers
One of the simplest and most straightforward ways to look at your success in social media is to measure the number of followers/subscribers you have. Over time, if you are posting content that people enjoy and if you are marketing yourself well, you should find people signing up and getting involved.
While this is the most obvious figure to concentrate on though, it can also be a mistake. As weíll see below, there are other factors that can provide more useful goals.
Engagement
But numbers alone donít paint a complete picture of your success. In fact, itís possible to buy several thousand followers for a relatively low sum but what youíll find is that this doesnít do much for you as those followers wonít be engaging with your content.
Engagement means that people are responding to your posts, that they are PMing you, that they are liking/favoriting your comments etc. In turn, this shows that theyíre actually finding what youíre sharing interesting and that makes them much more likely to buy the products you recommend or to share your posts with their own network.
You can usually see your engagement by looking at your stats/analytics. Consider that itís better to have a few highly engaged users than it is to have thousands of unengaged users ñ concentrate on this number!
Sales
If you were only to focus on one thing as a marketer, this would likely be the number youíd want to pay attention to. The number of sales you get will of course be a result of your followers and engagement and ultimately this is what those things will be serving: your profit.
If you want to keep things simple by looking at just one thing to drive up, this is the number to look at. Bear in mind though, that short-term sales wonít always mean long term sales, which is why itís normally better to look at a combination of factors.
</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7527420a5e3a7fd4f854e2c6bbaa28393a094d74.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/victormichael/mapping-out-your-social-networking-goals/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a07ef0bd-ad17-4f89-bd32-184b325c45b3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:13:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Social Network to Drive Traffic]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Using Social Network to Drive Traffic</h1><p>Using Social Networks to Drive Traffic to Your Offers
If you have a landing page or a squeeze page that is selling a product or collecting leads, then your business model will be simple: send as many people there as possible. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3aa62a556eb1a72235c4652b11f4ccca17512b81.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/victormichael/d7f60712-75f2-4016-bdbe-5a2fe50dd7c3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f60712-75f2-4016-bdbe-5a2fe50dd7c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:13:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>